(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Carol came back home from school.
When she went inside her house, she saw
a trail of ants.
The trail was so long.
There must have been over a thousand ants.
She was scared.
She slowly walked around it.
Where did it all start?
What are they after?
She followed the trail.
She ended up in her bedroom.
What would they want in there?
She looked at her bed.
There were cracker crumbs.
She never ate in her bed, though.
She looked at the package.
It was her brother's crackers.
She ran to her brother's room.
Did you see what you did?
Carol asked.
Her brother shook his head.
Carol showed him the ant trail and told
him to clean it up.